<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><users><all_users><user><email>af@unal.com</email><password>12345678</password><name>asdf</name><topMovies>Pelicula: 1920

Descripcion: An architect and his wife move into a castle that is slated to become a luxury hotel. But something inside is determined to stop the renovation.
Puntuacion: 6.4
Pelicula: 1922

Descripcion: "A farmer pens a confession admitting to his wife's murder; but her death is just the beginning of a macabre tale. Based on Stephen King's novella."
Puntuacion: 6.3
Pelicula: 13 sins

Descripcion: "A man agrees to appear on a game show with a $6 million prize. But as the challenges become more extreme; he realizes he's made a grave mistake."
Puntuacion: 6.3
Pelicula: #alive

Descripcion: "As a grisly virus rampages a city; a lone man stays locked inside his apartment; digitally cut off from seeking help and desperate to find a way out."
Puntuacion: 6.2
Pelicula: 122

Descripcion: "After an awful accident; a couple admitted to a grisly hospital are separated and must find each other to escape — before death finds them."
Puntuacion: 5.9
Pelicula: 1br

Descripcion: "Seeking her independence; a young woman moves to Los Angeles and settles into a cozy apartment complex with a disturbing sense of community."
Puntuacion: 5.8
Pelicula: 13 cameras

Descripcion: "Young parents-to-be Claire and Ryan move into a suburban rental home; unaware that someone is secretly watching their every move via hidden cameras."
Puntuacion: 5.1
Pelicula: 23:59

Descripcion: "When an army recruit is found dead; his fellow soldiers are forced to confront a terrifying secret that's haunting their jungle island training camp."
Puntuacion: 4.6
Pelicula: 6-5=2

Descripcion: "Six friends decide to undertake a grueling mountain trek; only to find that the difficulties in store for them are not merely physical."
Puntuacion: 4.2
Pelicula: 1st summoning

Descripcion: "Student filmmakers uncover occult rituals tied to an abandoned warehouse; then gradually realize the horror is closer than they think."
Puntuacion: 3.3
Pelicula: 13th

Descripcion: "In this thought-provoking documentary; scholars; activists and politicians analyze the criminalization of African Americans and the U.S. prison boom."
Puntuacion: 8.3
Pelicula: a family affair

Descripcion: The filmmaker hunts for the missing puzzle pieces of his family history during a visit with a complex and controversial figure: his grandmother.
Puntuacion: 8.1
Pelicula: 20 feet from stardom

Descripcion: "Winner of the 2014 Academy Award for Best Documentary Feature; this film takes a look at the world of backup vocalists and the legends they support."
Puntuacion: 7.4
Pelicula: 3 seconds divorce

Descripcion: "A Muslim women's activist group in India protests against oral divorces; starting a movement to reclaim their religious and constitutional rights."
Puntuacion: 7.2
Pelicula: 42 grams

Descripcion: "After launching a successful underground restaurant out of their apartment; an ambitious chef and his wife open an all-consuming upscale eatery."
Puntuacion: 7.1
Pelicula: a family affair

Descripcion: The filmmaker hunts for the missing puzzle pieces of his family history during a visit with a complex and controversial figure: his grandmother.
Puntuacion: 7.0
Pelicula: (t)error

Descripcion: This real-life look at FBI counterterrorism operations features access to both sides of a sting: the government informant and the radicalized target.
Puntuacion: 6.6
Pelicula: 14 minutes from earth

Descripcion: A Google executive boldly attempts a death-defying mission to travel to space and free-fall back to Earth without a rocket.
Puntuacion: 5.6
Pelicula: #cats_the_mewvie

Descripcion: "This pawesome documentary explores how our feline friends became online icons; from the earliest text memes to the rise of celebrity cat influencers."
Puntuacion: 5.3
Pelicula: #rucker50

Descripcion: This documentary celebrates the 50th anniversary of the Harlem sports program that has inspired countless city kids to become pro basketball players.
Puntuacion: 5.2
Pelicula: 100 meters

Descripcion: "A man who is diagnosed with multiple sclerosis responds by training for an Ironman triathlon; with his cranky father-in-law's help."
Puntuacion: 7.6
Pelicula: #friendbutmarried 2

Descripcion: "As Ayu and Ditto finally transition from best friends to newlyweds; a quick pregnancy creates uncertainty for the future of their young marriage."
Puntuacion: 6.8
Pelicula: 17 again

Descripcion: "Nearing a midlife crisis; thirty-something Mike wishes for a ""do-over"" – and that's exactly what he gets when he wakes up to find he's 17 again."
Puntuacion: 6.4
Pelicula: 10 jours en or

Descripcion: "When a carefree bachelor is unexpectedly left in charge of a young boy; the two embark on a road trip that will change both of their lives."
Puntuacion: 5.9
Pelicula: 2 alone in paris

Descripcion: "A bumbling Paris policeman is doggedly determined to capture the master thief that repeatedly eludes him; even when they're the last two men on Earth."
Puntuacion: 5.4
Pelicula: #realityhigh

Descripcion: "When nerdy high schooler Dani finally attracts the interest of her longtime crush; she lands in the cross hairs of his ex; a social media celebrity."
Puntuacion: 5.2
Pelicula: çarsi pazar

Descripcion: The slacker owner of a public bath house rallies his community to save it when a big developer comes to town to close it down and open a new mall.
Puntuacion: 5.2
Pelicula: #roxy

Descripcion: A teenage hacker with a huge nose helps a cool kid woo a girl that he’s secretly in love with.
Puntuacion: 5.1
Pelicula: 10 days in sun city

Descripcion: "After his girlfriend wins the Miss Nigeria pageant; a young man faces unexpected competition of his own when he joins her on a campaign in South Africa."
Puntuacion: 5.1
Pelicula: çok filim hareketler bunlar

Descripcion: "Vignettes of the summer holidays follow vacationers as they battle mosquitoes; suffer ruined plans and otherwise hit snags in their precious time off."
Puntuacion: 4.4
</topMovies><topSeries>Serie: a korean odyssey
Descripcion: A self-serving mythical creature's bid for invincibility backfires when he finds himself at the mercy of a woman who can see otherworldly beings.

Rating: 8.1
Serie: captive
Descripcion: "This documentary series reconstructs history's most complex; high-stakes hostage negotiations as kidnapping victims recount their terrifying ordeals."

Rating: 7.5
Serie: crazyhead
Descripcion: Bowling alley worker Amy and nonconformist Raquel kick some serious demon butt while also facing their inner demons as they navigate their early 20s.

Rating: 7.3
Serie: alone
Descripcion: "Equipped with limited resources; an isolated group of individuals is subjected to the harsh conditions of the wilderness and must survive — or tap out."

Rating: 6.8
Serie: chambers
Descripcion: "Haunted by eerie visions and sinister impulses after a heart transplant; a teenager tries to unmask the truth behind her donor's mysterious death."

Rating: 6.5
Serie: black summer
Descripcion: "In the dark; early days of a zombie apocalypse; complete strangers band together to find the strength they need to survive and get back to loved ones."

Rating: 6.4
Serie: a go! go! cory carson halloween
Descripcion: "Cory; Chrissy and Freddie are on the hunt for king-sized candy bars this Halloween! But are all the treats worth the trek to the spooky side of town?"

Rating: 6.0
Serie: backcountry
Descripcion: A weekend hike for urbanites Alex and Jenn takes a dangerous turn when they become lost deep in the remote territory of a menacing bear.

Rating: 5.8
Serie: ares
Descripcion: "Aiming to become part of Amsterdam's elite; an ambitious college student joins an exclusive society; unaware it's hiding a horrifying secret."

Rating: 5.6
Serie: betaal
Descripcion: "Hired to displace tribal villagers to make way for a new highway; officials unearth an old curse and an army of British soldier-zombies."

Rating: 5.3
Serie: a grand night in: the story of aardman
Descripcion: "Aardman Animations icons Wallace &amp; Gromit; Morph and more join fans and collaborators for a retrospective celebrating the studio's 40th anniversary."

Rating: 7.6
Serie: a year in space
Descripcion: Two astronauts attempt to brave a life in Earth's orbit on a record-setting mission to see if humans have the endurance to survive a flight to Mars.

Rating: 7.4
Serie: a perfect crime
Descripcion: "This docuseries investigates the 1991 killing of politician Detlev Rohwedder; an unsolved mystery at the heart of Germany's tumultuous reunification."

Rating: 7.3
Serie: 13th: a conversation with oprah winfrey &amp; ava duvernay
Descripcion: "Oprah Winfrey sits down with director Ava DuVernay to discuss her Oscar-nominated film; historical cycles of oppression and the broken prison system."

Rating: 7.1
Serie: 9 months that made you
Descripcion: "Witness the wonders of human gestation through cutting-edge CGI; and learn how those nine months inside the womb can affect all aspects of one's life."

Rating: 7.0
Serie: a family man
Descripcion: A ruthless corporate headhunter battles his rival for a promotion while dealing with a family crisis that threatens to derail his career.

Rating: 6.9
Serie: 7 days out
Descripcion: "Witness the excitement and drama behind the scenes in the seven days leading up to major live events in the worlds of sports; fashion; space and food."

Rating: 6.8
Serie: a 3 minute hug
Descripcion: This documentary captures the joy and heartbreak of families separated by the U.S.-Mexico border sharing a short but bittersweet reunion in 2018.

Rating: 6.5
Serie: a tale of two kitchens
Descripcion: "Mexico City restaurant star Gabriela Cámara opens sister eatery Cala in San Francisco; with a similar menu and unusually welcoming kitchen culture."

Rating: 6.3
Serie: 72 cutest animals
Descripcion: This series examines the nature of cuteness and how adorability helps some animal species to survive and thrive in a variety of environments.

Rating: 5.8
Serie: 100 days my prince
Descripcion: "Upon losing his memory; a crown prince encounters a commoner’s life and experiences unforgettable love as the husband to Joseon’s oldest bachelorette."

Rating: 7.6
Serie: 122
Descripcion: "After an awful accident; a couple admitted to a grisly hospital are separated and must find each other to escape — before death finds them."

Rating: 7.5
Serie: 100 things to do before high school
Descripcion: "Led by seventh-grader C.J.; three students who have been warned about the dangers of high school decide to make the best of their middle-school years."

Rating: 7.5
Serie: 100 things to do before high school
Descripcion: "Led by seventh-grader C.J.; three students who have been warned about the dangers of high school decide to make the best of their middle-school years."

Rating: 7.5
Serie: 12 years promise
Descripcion: "A pregnant teen is forced by her family to leave her boyfriend and assume a new identity in America; but 12 years later; the couple reunites in Korea."

Rating: 7.3
Serie: #blackaf
Descripcion: "Kenya Barris and his family navigate relationships; race and culture while grappling with their newfound success in this comedy series."

Rating: 6.8
Serie: 365 days
Descripcion: "A fiery executive in a spiritless relationship falls victim to a dominant mafia boss; who imprisons her and gives her one year to fall in love with him."

Rating: 6.7
Serie: 44 cats
Descripcion: "Paw-esome tales abound when singing furry friends Lampo; Milady; Pilou and Meatball band together."

Rating: 6.2
Serie: 9
Descripcion: "In a postapocalyptic world; rag-doll robots hide in fear from dangerous machines out to exterminate them; until a brave newcomer joins the group."

Rating: 5.4
Serie: 48 christmas wishes
Descripcion: "When a small town's letters to Santa accidentally go up in smoke; two elves venture out of the North Pole to retrieve every missing wish."

Rating: 3.9
</topSeries></user></all_users></users>